Marvin Leath papers, Inclusive: 1954-1994, undated; Bulk: 1979-1991
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Departments, Boards, and Commissions, 1979-1981; 4
  - Departments, 1979-1981; 1
    - State, Red China, General, 1980 (Box 274, Folder 9)
    - State, Rhodesia, 1979 (Box 274, Folder 10)
    - State, SALT II, 1980 (Box 274, Folder 11)
    - State, Vietnam Boat People, 1979 (Box 274, Folder 12)
    - Transportation, 1979 (Box 274, Folder 13)
    - Transportation, 1980 (Box 275, Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), 1979 (Box 275, Folder 2)
    - Transportation, FAA, 1980 (Box 275, Folder 3)
    - Transportation, FAA, KOXE Radio Station, Jamar, 1979 (Box 275, Folder 4)
    - Transportation, Federal Highway Administration, 1980 (Box 275, Folder 5)
    - Transportation, Grant Announcements, 1980 (Box 275, Folder 6)
    - Transportation, Information (1 of 3), 1979 (Box 275, Folder 7)
    - Transportation, Information (2 of 3), 1979 (Box 275, Folder 8)
    - Transportation, Information (3 of 3), 1979 (Box 275, Folder 9)
    - Transportation, Information, Annual Report, 1979 (Box 275, Folder 10)
    - Transportation, Information, Revenue Sharing, 1979 (Box 275, Folder 11)
    - Transportation, National Highway and Traffic Safety Administration, 1980 (Box 275, Folder 12)
    - Transportation, Competitive Bidding System, 1980 (Box 275, Folder 13)
    - Transportation, U.S. Coast Guard, 1980 (Box 275, Folder 14)
    - Treasury, 1979 (Box 276, Folder 1)
    - Treasury, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 2)
    - Treasury, Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms (ATF), 1979 (Box 276, Folder 3)
    - Treasury, Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 4)
    - Treasury, Information, 1979 (Box 276, Folder 5)
    - Treasury, Internal Revenue Service (IRS), 1979 (Box 276, Folder 6)
    - Treasury, Internal Revenue Service, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 7)
    - Treasury, Internal Revenue Service, Information, 1979 (Box 276, Folder 8)
  - Boards and Commissions, 1980-1981; 2
    - Air Control Board, 1981 (Box 276, Folder 9)
    - Animal Health Center, 1981 (Box 276, Folder 10)
    - Attorney General’s Office, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 11)
    - Attorney General's Office, 1981 (Box 276, Folder 12)
    - Brazos River Authority, 1981 (Box 276, Folder 13)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1981 (Box 276, Folder 14)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 15)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1981 (Box 276, Folder 16)
    - Commission for the Blind, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 17)
    - Commission on Alcoholism, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 18)
    - Commission on Alcoholism, 1981 (Box 276, Folder 19)
    - Commission on Arts and Humanities, 1981 (Box 276, Folder 20)
    - Commission on Civil Rights, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 21)
    - Commission on Wartime Relocation and Interment, 1981 (Box 276, Folder 22)
    - Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), 1981 (Box 276, Folder 23)
    - Comptroller of Public Accounts, 1981 (Box 276, Folder 24)
    - Consumer Product Safety Commission (CPSC), 1980 (Box 276, Folder 25)
    - Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1981 (Box 276, Folder 26)
    - Consumer Product Safety Commission, Cellulose Rule, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 27)
    - Energy Advisory Council, 1981 (Box 277, Folder 1)
    - Energy and Natural Resources Advisory Council, 1980 (Box 277, Folder 2)
    - Energy and Natural Resources, 1981 (Box 277, Folder 3)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1980 (Box 277, Folder 4)
    - Farm Credit Administration, 1980 (Box 277, Folder 5)
    - Farm Credit Administration, 1981 (Box 277, Folder 6)
    - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1980 (Box 277, Folder 7)
    - Federal Communications Commission, 1981 (Box 277, Folder 8)
    - Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC), 1980 (Box 277, Folder 9)
    - Federal Election Commission (FEC), 1980 (Box 277, Folder 10)
    - FEC, 1981 (Box 277, Folder 11)
    - Federal Home Loan Bank Board, 1981 (Box 277, Folder 12)
    - Federal Relations, 1981 (Box 277, Folder 13)
    - Federal Reserve System (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 277, Folder 14)
    - Federal Reserve System (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 277, Folder 15)
    - Federal Reserve System, 1980 (Box 277, Folder 16)
    - Federal Trade Commission, 1980 (Box 278, Folder 1)
    - Federal Trade Commission, 1981 (Box 278, Folder 2)
    - General Services Administration (GSA), 1980 (Box 278, Folder 3)
    - GSA, National Archives and Records Service (NARS), 1980 (Box 278, Folder 4)
    - Governor’s Office, 1980 (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Office, 1981 (Box 278, Folder 6)
    - Health Facilities Commission, 1980 (Box 278, Folder 7)
    - Heart of Texas Council of Governments (HOTCOG), 1981 (Box 278, Folder 8)
    - Heart of Texas Council of Governments, 1980 (Box 278, Folder 9)
    - House of Representatives, 1981 (Box 278, Folder 10)
    - House of Representatives, Region, Compacts, and District Committee, 1981 (Box 278, Folder 11)
    - Indian Commission, 1981 (Box 278, Folder 12)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), 1980 (Box 278, Folder 13)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1981 (Box 278, Folder 14)
    - Legal Services Corporation, 1980 (Box 278, Folder 15)
    - Legal Services Corporation (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 278, Folder 16)
    - Legal Services Corporation (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 278, Folder 17)
    - Lieutenant Governor, 1980 (Box 278, Folder 18)
    - Mental Health-Mental Retardation (MHMR), 1980 (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - Motor Vehicles Commission, 1980 (Box 279, Folder 2)
    - National Consumer Cooperative Bank, 1980 (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), 1980 (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - National Railroad Passenger Corporation (Amtrak), 1980 (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - Amtrak, 1981 (Box 279, Folder 6)
    - National Science Foundation, 1980 (Box 279, Folder 7)
    - National Science Foundation, 1981 (Box 279, Folder 8)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 1980 (Box 279, Folder 9)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Review Commission, 1980 (Box 279, Folder 10)
    - Office of Personnel Management, 1980 (Box 279, Folder 11)
    - Office of Personnel Management, 1981 (Box 279, Folder 12)
    - Office of Personnel Management, John W. Hamilton, 1981 (Box 279, Folder 13)
    - Pardons and Paroles, 1981 (Box 279, Folder 14)
    - Postal Rate Commission, 1980 (Box 279, Folder 15)
    - Railroad Commission of Texas, 1980 (Box 279, Folder 16)
    - Rehabilitation Commission, 1981 (Box 279, Folder 17)
    - Secretary of State’s Office, 1980 (Box 279, Folder 18)
    - Senate, Texas, 1981 (Box 279, Folder 19)
    - Small Business Administration (SBA), 1980 (Box 279, Folder 20)
    - SBA, 1981 (Box 279, Folder 21)
    - SBA, Disaster Loans, 1980 (Box 279, Folder 22)
    - SBA, Minority Contracts, 1981 (Box 279, Folder 23)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1980 (Box 279, Folder 24)
    - Texas Employment Commission, 1980 (Box 279, Folder 25)
    - Texas Employment Commission, 1981 (Box 279, Folder 26)
    - Texas Farmer’s Union, 1980 (Box 279, Folder 27)
    - Texas Sesquicentennial Commission, 1981 (Box 279, Folder 28)
    - Texas Public Utilities Commission (PUC), 1980 (Box 279, Folder 29)
    - United States International Trade Commission, 1980 (Box 279, Folder 30)
    - United Nations, 1980 (Box 279, Folder 31)
    - United Nations, 1981 (Box 279, Folder 32)
    - United Nations, Funding, 1980 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - United Nations, Membership Termination, 1981 (Box 280, Folder 2)
    - United States Postal Service (USPS), 1980 (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - United States Postal Service, 1981 (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - United States Postal Service, 9-Digit Zip Codes, 1981 (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - Veterans Administration (VA), 1980 (Box 280, Folder 6)
    - VA, 1981 (Box 280, Folder 7)
    - VA, A-76 Program, 1981 (Box 280, Folder 8)
    - VA, Marlin, Temple, and Waco Hospitals, 1980 (Box 280, Folder 9)
    - VA, Marlin, Temple, and Waco Hospitals, 1981 (Box 280, Folder 10)
    - VA, Length of Stay in VA Facilities, 1980 (Box 280, Folder 11)
    - VA, Establishment of Optometry Service, 1980 (Box 280, Folder 12)
    - Veterans Affairs Commission, 1981 (Box 280, Folder 13)
- Executive Branch, 1979-1987; 5
  This small series houses Executive Branch materials from 1979-1987 which cover White House tours and press releases. Also included are items related to Reagan’s economic proposals and personal letters to Marvin Leath.
  - Assistant to the President, 1979 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Commission on Executive, Legislative, and Judicial Salaries, 1981 (Box 281, Folder 2)
  - Council of Economic Advisors, 1981 (Box 281, Folder 3)
  - Executive Office of the President (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Executive Office of the President (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 281, Folder 5)
  - Office of Management and Budget (OMB), 1979 (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - Office of Management and Budget, 1981 (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - Office of the Vice-President, 1979 (Box 281, Folder 8)
  - Office of the Vice-President, 1981 (Box 281, Folder 9)
  - Office of the White House Secretary, 1979 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - President of the United States (POTUS), 1979 (Box 281, Folder 11)
  - POTUS, 1980 (Box 281, Folder 12)
  - POTUS, 1981 (Box 281, Folder 13)
  - POTUS, President’s Proposals, 1980 (Box 281, Folder 14)
  - Presidential Speeches (Comments On), 1979 (Box 281, Folder 15)
  - Reagan’s Budget Cuts “Pro” (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 282, Folder 1)
  - Reagan’s Budget Cuts “Pro” (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 282, Folder 2)
  - Reagan’s Economic Program (1 of 5), 1981 (Box 282, Folder 3)
  - Reagan’s Economic Program (2 of 5), 1981 (Box 282, Folder 4)
  - Reagan’s Economic Program (3 of 5), 1981 (Box 282, Folder 5)
  - Reagan’s Economic Program (4 of 5), 1981 (Box 282, Folder 6)
  - Reagan’s Economic Program (5 of 5), 1981 (Box 282, Folder 7)
  - Reagan’s Tax Proposal (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 282, Folder 8)
  - Reagan’s Tax Proposal (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 283, Folder 1)
  - Reagan’s Tax Proposal, In-District, “Con” (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 283, Folder 2)
  - Reagan’s Tax Proposal, In-District, “Con” (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 283, Folder 3)
  - Reagan’s Tax Proposal, In-District, “Pro” (1 of 4), 1981 (Box 283, Folder 4)
  - Reagan’s Tax Proposal, In-District, “Pro” (2 of 4), 1981 (Box 283, Folder 5)
  - Reagan’s Tax Proposal, In-District, “Pro” (3 of 4), 1981 (Box 283, Folder 6)
  - Reagan’s Tax Proposal, In-District, “Pro” (4 of 4), 1981 (Box 283, Folder 7)
  - Reagan’s Tax Proposal, Out of District, “Con”, 1981 (Box 284, Folder 1)
  - Reagan’s Tax Proposal, Out of District, “Pro” (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 284, Folder 2)
  - Reagan’s Tax Proposal, Out of District, “Pro” (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - White House, 1979 (Box 284, Folder 4)
  - White House, 1981 (Box 284, Folder 5)
  - White House, 1983-1987 (Box 284, Folder 6)
  - White House, Conference on Aging, 1981 (Box 284, Folder 7)
  - White House, Conference on Aging (Phase 1 Activities) and Governor’s Commission on Aging Biennial Report, 1981 (Box 284, Folder 8)
  - White House, Conference on Families, 1980 (Box 285, Folder 1)
  - White House, Conference on Library and Information Services, 1980 (Box 285, Folder 2)
  - White House, Conference on Small Business, 1979 (Box 285, Folder 3)
  - White House, Fellowships, 1981 (Box 285, Folder 4)
  - White House Office, 1980 (Box 285, Folder 5)
  - White House Press Secretary (1 of 3), 1979 (Box 285, Folder 6)
  - White House Press Secretary (2 of 3), 1979 (Box 285, Folder 7)
  - White House Press Secretary (3 of 3), 1979 (Box 285, Folder 8)
  - White House, Press Kit, 1979 (Box 285, Folder 9)
  - White House, Press Releases, 1980 February (Box 285, Folder 10)
  - White House, Press Releases, March, April, July, 1980 (Box 285, Folder 11)
  - White House, Rural Development Initiatives, 1979 (Box 285, Folder 12)
  - White House, Tour Requests, 1983-1984 (Box 285, Folder 13)
  - White House, Tour Requests, 1981 (Box 286, Folder 1)
  - White House, Tour Requests, 1979-1980 (Box 286, Folder 2)
  - White House, Tour Requests, 1985-1986 (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - White House, Tour Requests, 1982-1983 (Box 286, Folder 4)
- Legislative, 1978-1991, undated; 6
  The extensive Legislative section includes three subseries: 1. general legislative documents arranged alphabetically by topic; 2. Leath-authored bills from 1979-1981; and 3. Congressional bills of note from the 96th, 97th, 98th, 99th, 100th, and 101st Congresses. The second and third subseries are subdivided by Congress. Of interest in this section are the folders on the House Armed Services Committee Chairmanship and the Veterans Affairs materials, which highlight two of Leath’s largest legislative priorities. Additionally, a substantial cadre of bills against desecration of the American flag affords a fascinating perspective on Leath’s views on patriotism. Heavy sampling occurred in subseries 2 and subseries 3, sub-subseries’ 5-6 while moderate sampling happened in subseries 3, sub-subseries’ 1-4. Many folders with duplicate bills or bills with no connection to Leath were omitted or consolidated in subseries’ 2-3.
  - General, 1978-1991, undated; 1
    - General (1 of 4), 1979 (Box 286, Folder 5)
    - General (2 of 4), 1979 (Box 286, Folder 6)
    - General (3 of 4), 1979 (Box 286, Folder 7)
    - General (4 of 4), 1979 (Box 287, Folder 1)
    - General (1 of 3), 1980 (Box 287, Folder 2)
    - General (2 of 3), 1980 (Box 287, Folder 3)
    - General (3 of 3), 1980 (Box 287, Folder 4)
    - General, Opinion Ballot, 1980 (Box 287, Folder 5)
    - Aging, Select Committee on, 1979 (Box 287, Folder 6)
    - Aging, Select Committee on, 1980 (Box 287, Folder 7)
    - Aging, Select Committee on, 1981 (Box 288, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 288, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 288, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture, 1980 (Box 288, Folder 4)
    - Agriculture (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 288, Folder 5)
    - Agriculture (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 288, Folder 6)
    - Agriculture, Act of 1977 & Food and Agriculture Act of 1949, 1979 (Box 289, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture, Agricultural Extension Service, undated (Box 289, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture, Agriculture Stabilization and Conservation Service (ASCS), 1981 (Box 289, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture, ASCS, Black's Feed Mill, 1981 (Box 289, Folder 4)
    - Agriculture, American Agriculture Movement, 1979 (Box 289, Folder 5)
    - Agriculture, Appropriations, 1979 (Box 289, Folder 6)
    - Agriculture, Beekeeper’s Indemnity, 1980 (Box 289, Folder 7)
    - Agriculture, Commodity Credit Corporation Graph Scale, 1981 (Box 289, Folder 8)
    - Agriculture, Committee Testimony by Leath, 1979 (Box 289, Folder 9)
    - Agriculture, Farm Bill, 1981 (Box 289, Folder 10)
    - Agriculture, Federal Crop Insurance, 1979 (Box 289, Folder 11)
    - Agriculture, Federal Crop Insurance, H.R. 4119, 1980 (Box 289, Folder 12)
    - Agriculture, Federal Grain Inspection Service (FGIS), 1981 (Box 289, Folder 13)
    - Agriculture, Farmers Home Administration (FmHA), 1981 (Box 289, Folder 14)
    - Agriculture, Farmers Home Administration, Grant Announcements, 1981 (Box 289, Folder 15)
    - Agriculture, Food Stamps, 1979 (Box 289, Folder 16)
    - Agriculture, Food Stamps, 1980 (Box 290, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture, Food Stamps, Cons, 1981 (Box 290, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture, Food Stamps, Pros, 1981 (Box 290, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture, Grain Imported by Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC), 1979 (Box 290, Folder 4)
    - Agriculture, H.J. Res. 460, Hunger Survey, 1980 (Box 290, Folder 5)
    - Agriculture, H.R. 2172, Sugar Bill, 1979 (Box 290, Folder 6)
    - Agriculture, Lands Protection, H.R. 2551, 1980 (Box 290, Folder 7)
    - Agriculture, Office of the Inspector General, 1981 (Box 290, Folder 8)
    - Agriculture, Peanut Program (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 290, Folder 9)
    - Agriculture, Peanut Program (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 290, Folder 10)
    - Agriculture, Plant Variety Protection, H.R. 999, S. 23, 1980 (Box 291, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture, Pork Issue, 1981 (Box 291, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture, Program Report and Environmental Impact Statements, 1981 (Box 291, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture, Research Material on Food Stamps, 1980 (Box 291, Folder 4)
    - Agriculture, Resource and Conservation, 1981 (Box 291, Folder 5)
    - Agriculture, Rural Electrification Administration, 1981 (Box 291, Folder 6)
    - Agriculture, Soil Conservation, 1979 (Box 291, Folder 7)
    - Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service, 1981 (Box 291, Folder 8)
    - Agriculture, Soil Conservation, Watershed, 1981 (Box 291, Folder 9)
    - Agriculture, Texas, Foreign Trade, 1979 (Box 291, Folder 10)
    - Air Traffic Controllers, 1981 (Box 291, Folder 11)
    - Appropriations, 1979 (Box 291, Folder 12)
    - Appropriations, 1980 (Box 292, Folder 1)
    - Appropriations, 1981 (Box 292, Folder 2)
    - Appropriations, District of Columbia, 1979 (Box 292, Folder 3)
    - Appropriations, H.R. 4389 Comprehensive Slate Grant Program, 1979 (Box 292, Folder 4)
    - Appropriations, Social Services/Child Welfare (H.R. 3434), 1980 (Box 292, Folder 5)
    - Appropriations, Subcommittee on Labor (Health, Education, Welfare [HEW]- Occupational Safety & Health Administration [OSHA] Budget), 1979 (Box 292, Folder 6)
    - Appropriations, Testimony on Energy and Water Development, 1979 April 4 (Box 292, Folder 7)
    - Armed Services, 1979 (Box 292, Folder 8)
    - Armed Services, 1980 (Box 292, Folder 9)
    - Armed Services, Fort Hood Cuts, 1979 (Box 292, Folder 10)
    - Armed Services, Correspondence from Leath, 1981 (Box 292, Folder 11)
    - Armed Services, Correspondence to Leath, 1981 (Box 292, Folder 12)
    - Armed Services, Divorced Military Wives, 1981 (Box 293, Folder 1)
    - Armed Services, Draft, 1979 (Box 293, Folder 2)
    - Armed Services, Draft, 1980 (Box 293, Folder 3)
    - Armed Services, Draft, 1981 (Box 293, Folder 4)
    - Armed Services, Draft, Pro, 1981 (Box 293, Folder 5)
    - Armed Services, Impact Aid, 1981 (Box 293, Folder 6)
    - Armed Services, Leath Testimony, Military Personnel, 1979 March 20 (Box 293, Folder 7)
    - Armed Services, Military Compensation, 1980 (Box 293, Folder 8)
    - Armed Services, Non-Appointed Funds Panel, 1979 (Box 293, Folder 9)
    - Armed Services, Retired Military Pay, 1980 (Box 293, Folder 10)
    - Armed Services, Subcommittee on Seapower, Congressional Letter to Press, 1979 (Box 293, Folder 11)
    - Armed Services, Testimony, Civilian Cutbacks, 1979 April 2 (Box 293, Folder 12)
    - Assassinations, Select Committee on, 1979 (Box 293, Folder 13)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs (1 of 3), 1979 (Box 293, Folder 14)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs (2 of 3), 1979 (Box 294, Folder 1)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs (3 of 3), 1979 (Box 294, Folder 2)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, 1980 (Box 294, Folder 3)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 294, Folder 4)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 294, Folder 5)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, Broken Cranston Funding, H.R. 6197, 1980 (Box 294, Folder 6)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, Chrysler Loan Guarantee, H.R. 5860, 1980 (Box 294, Folder 7)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, Depository Institutions Deregulation Committee, 1981 (Box 294, Folder 8)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, Federal Open Market Committee, H.R. 4998, 1980 (Box 294, Folder 9)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, Gold Standard, H.R. 5658, 1980 (Box 294, Folder 10)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, H.R. 2658, 1979 (Box 294, Folder 11)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, H.R. 3864 (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 294, Folder 12)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, H.R. 3864 (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 295, Folder 1)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, H.R. 3875, 1979 (Box 295, Folder 2)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, Interest Rates, 1981 (Box 295, Folder 3)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, Monetary Control, 1981 (Box 295, Folder 4)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, Monetary Market Funds (1 of 3), 1981 (Box 295, Folder 5)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, Monetary Market Funds (2 of 3), 1981 (Box 295, Folder 6)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, Monetary Market Funds (3 of 3), 1981 (Box 295, Folder 7)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, Housing and Community Development, 1980 (Box 295, Folder 8)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, Share Drafts (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 295, Folder 9)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, Share Drafts (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 295, Folder 10)
    - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs, Share Drafts, H.R. 4986, 1980 (Box 296, Folder 1)
    - Budget, Balanced Budget, 1981 (Box 296, Folder 2)
    - Budget, Big Government/Big Spending, 1980 (Box 296, Folder 3)
    - Budget, Big Government/Big Spending, 1981 (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - Budget, Budget Committee Briefings (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 296, Folder 5)
    - Budget, Budget Committee Briefings (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 296, Folder 6)
    - Budget, Budget Reconciliation (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 296, Folder 7)
    - Budget, Budget Reconciliation (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 296, Folder 8)
    - Budget, Congressional Budget Office (CBO) Budget Analysis (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 296, Folder 9)
    - Budget, Congressional Budget Office (CBO) Budget Analysis (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 297, Folder 1)
    - Budget, Cost of Living Adjustment (COLA), 1980 (Box 297, Folder 2)
    - Budget, COLA, Cons, 1981 (Box 297, Folder 3)
    - Budget, COLA, Pros (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 297, Folder 4)
    - Budget, COLA, Pros (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 297, Folder 5)
    - Budget, Davis-Bacon Reform, 101st Congress, 1990 (Box 297, Folder 6)
    - Budget, Defense Task Force, 1989 (Box 297, Folder 7)
    - Budget, Department of State Briefing Book (1 of 3), 1986-1987 (Box 297, Folder 8)
    - Budget, Department of State Briefing Book (2 of 3), 1986-1987 (Box 297, Folder 9)
    - Budget, Department of State Briefing Book (3 of 3), 1986-1987 (Box 298, Folder 1)
    - Budget, Federal Budget (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 298, Folder 2)
    - Budget, Federal Budget (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 298, Folder 3)
    - Budget, Federal Budget (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 298, Folder 4)
    - Budget, Federal Budget (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 298, Folder 5)
    - Budget, Federal Budget (1 of 4), 1981 (Box 299, Folder 1)
    - Budget, Federal Budget (2 of 4), 1981 (Box 299, Folder 2)
    - Budget, Federal Budget (3 of 4), 1981 (Box 299, Folder 3)
    - Budget, Federal Budget (4 of 4), 1981 (Box 299, Folder 4)
    - Budget, Federal Budget, Information, 1982 (Box 299, Folder 5)
    - Budget, First Concurrent Budget Resolution, Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (LEAA), 1980 (Box 299, Folder 6)
    - Budget, FY 1980, First Concurrent Budget Resolution, General (Box 300, Folder 1)
    - Budget, FY 1980, First Concurrent Budget Resolution, Saturday Mail (Box 300, Folder 2)
    - Budget, FY 1980, Human and Community Resources (Box 300, Folder 3)
    - Budget, FY 1980, Tax Expenditures and Tax Policy (Box 300, Folder 4)
    - Budget, FY 1981, First Concurrent Budget Resolution (Box 300, Folder 5)
    - Budget, FY 1981, Gramm Lotta Proposal (1 of 3) (Box 300, Folder 6)
    - Budget, FY 1981, Gramm Lotta Proposal (2 of 3) (Box 300, Folder 7)
    - Budget, FY 1981, Gramm Lotta Proposal (3 of 3) (Box 300, Folder 8)
    - Budget, FY 1981, Jones Budget/Senior Citizens (1 of 4) (Box 300, Folder 9)
    - Budget, FY 1981, Jones Budget/Senior Citizens (2 of 4) (Box 301, Folder 1)
    - Budget, FY 1981, Jones Budget/Senior Citizens (3 of 4) (Box 301, Folder 2)
    - Budget, FY 1981, Jones Budget/Senior Citizens (4 of 4) (Box 301, Folder 3)
    - Budget, FY 1986, “92 Group” Plans, 1985 (Box 301, Folder 4)
    - Budget, FY 1986, Actual Year-End Budget (Box 301, Folder 5)
    - Budget, FY 1986, Amtrak, 1985 (Box 301, Folder 6)